tolearnenglish.com 2003-12-07

# Code of conduct

**(Instant translation/definition) **

**Privacy Policy**

**We are committed to protecting your privacy while you are visiting www.ToLearnEnglish.com (the "Site"). Accordingly, ToLearnEnglish created the ToLearnEnglish.com Privacy Policy.  
The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you as to what information may be collected from you when visiting the Site, how such information will be used by ToLearnEnglish and/or other persons or entities, with whom such information may be shared, your choices regarding the collection, use and distribution of such information, your ability to edit, update, correct or delete such information and the security procedures that we have implemented to protect your privacy.   
**

**The Information We Collect**

**When you visit the site, no information is stored into a database. We don't ask you to register or to give us personal information. Yet, when you join our mailing list, your e-mail address is -of course- stored into a database (run by YahooGroups.com).**

**Please also be aware that ToLearnEnglish uses commonly employed Internet technologies to collect additional information. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are transferred by a web site and stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies; although you may choose disable your web browser's acceptance of cookies. We don't have any access to these cookies.  
**

**In addition, ToLearnEnglish has several special relationships with other web sites ("Partners"). In some instances, the site or area of the site is "co-branded" with or "powered by" a Partner's logo or a Partner's name may appear in the URL. When you provide registration data on a co-branded site or area, personal and/or aggregate data may be shared with that partner. You should review the individual privacy policies of these partners and make an informed decision about whether to continue. You may opt-out of sharing your information with that partner by choosing not to register or use that site or service. For a listing of all of ToLearnEnglish Partners with which we maintain information sharing arrangements, please contact us.  
**

**Banner ads  
ToLearnEnglish uses leading third-party advertising companies to display ads on our Site and through our tools. ToLearnEnglish shares web site usage information about visitors to the Site with these companies for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on the Site and other web sites. For this purpose, we and our third-party advertising company note some of the pages you visit on the Site through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs). The information collected by our third-party advertising company through the use of these pixel tags is not personally identifiable. In addition, our third-party advertising company may display banner ads that contain "cookies." The "cookies" received with these banner ads are collected by our third-party advertising company and we do not have access to this information. **

** Public Forums  
The Site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, instant messaging, and web polls available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose information.  
**

**Protection of Children  
The protection and safety of children is very important to ToLearnEnglish and we therefore encourage parents and guardians to participate in and supervise the online activities of their children. **

**  
Third Party Links  
The Site may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties over which we have absolutely no control. The information practices of those web sites are not covered by this privacy policy. Any information you provide to third party web sites will be governed under the terms of each such web site's privacy policy. We have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content, actions or policies of third party web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all third party web sites that link to the Site because such privacy policies may be materially different from this privacy policy.   
**

**Questions, Comments or Concerns  
If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, or if you are concerned that we have not followed the principles set forth in this privacy policy, please contact [Laurent.Camus@ToLearnEnglish.com](mailto:Laurent.Camus@ToLearnEnglish.com)  
**

**Other Information You Should Know  
ToLearnEnglish may disclose the information that we collect about you when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to us or to others. We may also disclose your information when we believe the law requires it. ToLearnEnglish may, in its sole discretion, revise this privacy policy at any time and all such revisions shall be effective when posted. Accordingly, ToLearnEnglish encourages you to periodically review this privacy policy in order to keep apprised of ToLearnEnglish' current privacy practices.   
Thank you for trusting ToLearnEnglish.com  
****  
**

>  

****
